(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-31T12:43:52.149671",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
今日起きた朝はなんだか
Wake up this morning, I feel...
いつもより眠って
even sleepier than usual.
昨日の夜ずっと漫画を読んでたら眠れなくて
Reading manga all night long last night made me wide awake,
今頃そちはどこで何してるのかななんて
I wonder where and what I'm dreaming about right now?
考えてたら心が少し軽くなるんだ
Thinking about it makes my heart feel a little lighter.
これは内緒なんだけど昨日読んだ漫画の
This is a secret, but it's a bit like the manga I read last night.
主人公に君がちょっと似てて考えたよ、ねえ、一緒に食べよう!
Thinking about you and me, let's eat together, let's eat together!
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち共有したくて
Sharing the exact same feeling today,
そう、食べるだけでも素敵なことなくてもいつもの君でいいんだよ、一緒に食べよう!
even if it's just eating, I'm happy just being with you as always, so let's eat together!
バックステージずっとは言えない秘密の君の日々だけれど
The backstage is a secret only you and I know,
最近の私は少しきらきらなんだ
recently my days have been sparkling a little.
こんなにストレートに嫌なことあっても君に会えるともっとにやけちゃってさ、ねえ、一緒に食べよう!
Even if strange things happen, as long as I can see you, I get even more tired out, so let's eat together!
一人よりきっと楽しくなるから
Eating with you makes it so much more fun,
そう、食べるだけでも素敵なことがないから変なこと考えないでよ、まあいいけどさ、ねえ、君がくれる
so don't think about anything weird, though it doesn't really matter, I hope you'll give me...
言葉一つ、一つ、嬉しくなったり楽しくなったり不思議な魔法を 感じるってこと
just one word, just one word, making me so happy, making me so fun, feeling that mysterious magic, that's what it means!
ねえ、一緒に食べよう!
So let's eat together, let's eat together!
昼昼昼食べよ
Let's eat lunch, lunch, lunch!
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち共有したくて
I just want to share the same feeling with you,
そう昼昼昼昼昼昼だけでも
Yes, even if it's just for lunch, lunch, lunch!
全部別なことがなくても
Even if nothing else is different,
いつでも君がいいんだよ一緒に食べよ
Whenever you're the one, let's eat together!
ご飯ねー！わあ、ご飯ね！ご飯ね！ご飯ね！
Rice! Yay, rice! Rice! Rice!
このライブをご期生オレンジ担当の
For this live, the 5th generation orange rep,
桃鈴ねねです！よろしくねー！
I am Momosuzu Nene! Nice to meet you!
えー、というわけで、みんな、今日のねの、
Um, so everyone, for Nene's free solo
YouTubeの無料のソロライブ、えねねいろライブにお越しいただきまして、皆様も本当にありがとうございました！イエーイ！
YouTube live, "Neneiro Live," today, thank you all so much! Yay!
イエーイ！ちょっと待ってねー。
Yay! Hold on a second.
なあ、ただいまー！お帰りー！
Now, I'm back! Welcome back!
はい、というわけで、え、今日がですね、ランチビズミーの完成版のダンスの、え、お披露目だったんですけれどもち、まあ、ちょっとね
So, today was the debut of the completed dance version of "Lunch with me," but um...
なんかちょっと間違えちゃったけど、え、どうでしたでしょうか？
I messed up a bit in some parts, but um, how was it?
え、コメント、コメント、あ、かわいい、あ、めっっちゃかわいい、吐息ASMR助かる、ありがとう！
Ah, comments, comments. "So cute," "Super cute," "Sighing ASMR is a lifesaver, thanks!"
はい、みんな、えっと今日はですね、え、ハッシュタグ、え、ねねいろライブ、普段からねねが、え、配信タグとして使ってるタグが、今日の、え、ライブのタグになりますので、よかったらたくさんツイートしてね！
Right, so today's hashtag is `#ねねいろライブ`, the tag Nene usually uses for streams, so please tweet a lot!
はい、というわけでねの息もね、だいぶ落ち着いてきましたので、え、2曲目にいきたいと思います！とゆわけで、え、聞いてください。
Alright, so Nene's breathing has calmed down quite a bit, so I'd like to move on to the second song! Please listen.
冒険でしょでしょ？
"Bouken desho desho?"
答えはいつも私の胸に
The answer is always in my heart.
冒険でしょでしょ？
It's an adventure, right?
なぜだろうあなたを選んだ私です
Why did I choose you? That's me.
もう止まらない運命様から決められた恋より
It's already unstoppable, more than a destiny-ordained love,
逢引真似だけじゃつまらないの指先
Just imitating secret rendezvous is boring, our fingertips
感じるまま感じることだけをするよ
I'll just do what I feel, exactly as I feel it!
冒険でしょでしょ？本当かうそに変わる世界で
It's an adventure, right? In a world where truth turns into lies,
夢があるから強くなるのよ誰のためじゃない
I get stronger because I have dreams, not for anyone else's sake.
一緒に来てくだ祭どこまでも自由な私を見てよね
Please come with me all the way and look at the free me!
明日過去になった今日の今が奇跡アイ・ウィル・リメイン・ユー
Today, which will become yesterday tomorrow, is a miracle. I will remain you.
戻れないどこまで行かなきゃつまらない
We can't turn back, how far do we have to go? It's boring otherwise.
さあ、生い茂て決めてる願いを鏡に投げたマイ・ディスティニー
Now, throw the wish you've cultivated into the mirror, my destiny.
体ごと受け止めれたらヤー、マイ・フライ
Catch me with your whole body—yeah, my fly!
驚かせて驚いて笑顔になろう
Surprise me, be surprised, and let's smile!
始まりでしょでしょ？綺麗が闇を照らすみたいに
It's a beginning, right? Just like beauty illuminates the darkness,
私の力あなたの涙どちらも悲しいの
my power and your tears are both sad.
現実に揺れる繊細な心が傷つくのはいや
A delicate heart shaking in reality getting hurt—I hate that.
思い出しだいつもいつも胸の奥に
Whenever I remember, deep in my chest always, always...
答えが……
The answer is...
普通じゃないのが当然なら
If it's only natural not to be normal,
答える私は何ができる
what can I, who answers, do?
普通でも普通じゃなくて
Normal, yet not normal,
感じるまま感じることだけをするよ
I'll just do what I feel, exactly as I feel it.
冒険でしょでしょ!?
It's an adventure, right?!
ホントが嘘に変わる世界で
In a world where truth turns into lies,
夢があるから強くなるのよ 誰のためじゃない 始まりでしょ
I grow stronger because of my dreams, an adventure not for anyone else, right?
始まりなんでしょ?
It's the beginning, right?
綺麗が闇を照らすみたいに 私とあなた 防衛線の途中
Like beauty illuminating the dark, you and I are on a defense line
一緒に進んでく
advancing together
どこまでも自由に 現実を越えて明日過去になった今日の今が奇跡
freely everywhere, going beyond reality; today's present, tomorrow's past, is a miracle.
確かだな未来を
Let's grasp a certain future,
未来を
the future,
つかもう 未来を
let's grasp the future,
i believe you
ありがとうございました！ え、冒険でしょでしょお聞きしました！
Thank you very much! Um, you heard "Bouken Desho Desho?"!
えーというわけで、えーちょっと先にね、ステージの移動はしたいと思いますので
Um, so, um, I'd like to move the stage first,
と思ったけど、もうちょっと時間待っててわ。えーと冒険でしょでしょお聞きいただきました。
or so I thought, but wait just a little longer. Um, you heard "Bouken Desho Desho?".
えっとね、3Dライブの、3Dお披露目のときに一曲ね、あの
Um, you see, at the 3D live, 3D debut reveal, I sang one song, um,
鈴谷ハルカから一曲歌ったんですけど、今回もね、もう一曲歌いたいなと思って冒険でしょでしょ選んでみました。
Suzuka Haruka and I sang one song, but this time too, I wanted to sing another song, so I chose "Bouken Desho Desho?".
みんな知ってましたか？ねえねえこの曲大好き！やったー！
Did everyone know it? Hey hey, I love this song so much! Yay!
はい、じゃあというわけでね、あ、先にステージ移動したいと思います。すー、移動！
Yes, so with that, ah, I'd like to move the stage first. S-, move!
あー、きたきたきたきた！あ、よかった。あーねえの声聞こえる？みんな。
Ah, it's here, it's here, it's here! Ah, great. Ah, can you hear Nene's voice? Everyone.
あーどうもどうも あ、知ってた？めっちゃ懐かしかった。本当、ねえねえかは結構、芸歴声優なんだけど
Ah, hello, hello! Ah, you knew? It brought back memories. Really, Nene is quite a veteran voice actress, but
困ったな。ちょっとね、ここでね、あの、フリートークの時間とってもいいっていうことだったので、
Oh dear. Um, you know, we could take some time for free talk here, so
前回ね、あの3Dお披露目の時にはできなかった、この桜並木のステージで、え、ねっこのみんなとちょっと撮影会をしたいと思ってますので、
last time, um, at the 3D reveal we couldn't do it, on this cherry blossom lined stage, um, I want to do a photoshoot session with all the nekko, so um,
ねっこ、あ、いる？いるかな？あれ？あ、ねっこのみんなさ、ねっこ
nekko, ah, are you here? Are you here? Huh? Ah, everyone in nekko, nekko
あ！いた！いるじゃん！おいうえ
Ah! There you are! You are here! Oi ue
よいしょ。お。よいしょ。
Heave-ho. Oh. Heave-ho.
えへへへ お、お、あ、こうだな？よいしょ。
Ehehehe. Oh, oh, ah, like this? Heave-ho.
こっちも。こっちも。
This side too. This side too.
あ、ちょっとハンドパワーになっちゃう。あ、ハンドパワーになっちゃった。
Ah, it's becoming hand power. Ah, it became hand power.
イエーイ！あ、ちょっとこっちの子、うわ、こっち持ってるから。人参の子にしようかな。
Yay! Ah, this child here, wow, holding this. I'll make it the carrot child.
あ、ちょっと待てよ。うーん。
Ah, wait a minute. Hmm.
なんか、あれ？まって、あのねね画面ガシってやってない？ねっこのみんなの。ガシガシ、ガシガシ。
Somehow, huh? Wait, didn't Nene smash the screen? Everyone in nekko's. Smash smash, smash smash.
ああそっか、今日はスケルトンタイプのなんだ。スケルトンなんだね。
Ah right, today it's a skeleton type. It's a skeleton, huh.
あそっかそっか。撮った？みんな。
Ah right right. Did you take it? Everyone.
ちょっと待てよ。ん、ん、あ、今日ちょっとすけ、あ、あ、これでもみんな！
Wait a minute. Hmm, hmm, ah, today a little suke, ah, ah, even so everyone!
あ、これで撮って！あ、すごい、いいじゃん！あの、セクシーアングルとともに。あ、波？
Ah, take it with this! Ah, amazing, that's great! Along with, um, a sexy angle. Ah, Nami?
波もはんがんんばってる？はい。脇。
Is Nami also doing her best? Yes. Armpit.
あ、どうもどうも！あ、アップどうも！アップどうも！あ、あ、波が喜んじゃう！
Ah, hello hello! Ah, thanks for the close-up! Thanks for the close-up! Ah, ah, Nami is getting happy!
あー！どうみんな撮れた？ちょっと。よし。
Ah! How is it, did everyone take it? A little. Alright.
いい感じかな、みんな。
Is it a good feeling, everyone?
あ、で、で、う、浮いててくれてありがとね、ごめんね。乗れる？あ、いいじゃんかわいい！あ、かわいい！
Ah, an-, d-, th-, thanks for floating, sorry. Can you ride? Ah, nice, cute! Ah, cute!
ああ、めっちゃいい感じ！じゃあちょっと、ちょっと、
Ah, super good feeling! Well then a little, a little,
ねぇ ちょっと風送るからさ
Hey, I'm gonna send some wind over,
いい？行くよ。ふー
so ready? Here I go. Fuu—
ふーーははははっ
Fuuu— hahaha!
お返しできた
I blew it back!
ふーーーーーーっ
Fuuuuu—!
いい感じ？みんな取れた？
How's that? Did everyone catch it?
どうですか？
How is it?
こんなのとかな こんなのとかな
Like this, or like this?
こんなのとかな もう撮り放題！
Or like this? You can take as many as you want!
ああ、助かる。あ、全身斜めのアングル助かる！
Ah, that helps. Full-body diagonal angles help!
あ、なんてセクシーなんだ！
Ah, how sexy!
素晴らしい
Wonderful.
ああ、やっぱ違うな！やっぱプロのカメラマンさん違うな！
Ah, yeah, it's different! Pro cameramen really are different!
やっぱ分かってるわ、ねねのセクシーな角度。
They totally get Nene's sexy angles.
最高！ありがとうございます。
Awesome! Thank you very much.
ねっこのみんなもありがとーー！
Nekko everyone, thank you so much!
よしよし
Good, good.
じゃあね、準備が整ったということですですので
Well then, since preparations are all set,
え、次の曲に行きたいと思います。
um, I'd like to move on to the next song.
え、次の曲はですね、ちょっとこの桜並木に合わせつけてしっとりとした曲をお送りしたいと思います。
Um, the next song, I'd like to deliver a soothing song fitting these cherry blossom trees.
過去のねねのライブで一度だけ登場したことのある曲です。
It's a song that has only appeared once in Nene's past live performances.
それでは聞いてください。
So please listen.
エブリシング
EverySing
すれ違う 時 の 中 で
Of all the times I've walked past you,
あなた と めぐり逢えた
I finally got to cross paths with you.
不思議 ね 願い た 奇跡 が
Isn't it wondrous that the miracle I'd been wishing for
こんな に も 側 に ある なんて
was this close to me?
会い たい 思い の まま
I wish I could see you, but moment after moment
会え ない 時間 だけ が
of not getting to see you keeps going by,
過ぎ て く 扉 すり抜け て また 思い出し て
slipping through the door, and then I remember you again,
あの 人 と 笑い合う あなた を
laughing with him.
愛しき人よ 悲しませないで
My beloved, don't be sad.
泣き疲れて眠る夜もあるから
Some nights, you'll cry yourself to sleep.
過去を見ないで見つめて私だけ
Don't look at the past, just lay your eyes on me and nothing else.
You're everything
あなたが想うより強く優しい嘘ならいらない
I love you more than you think. I don't need your kind lies,
欲しいのはあなた
all I want is you.
どれくらいの時間を永遠と呼べるのだろう
How much time would you consider 'eternity'?
果てしなく遠い未来なら あなたと行きたい あなたと覗いてみたい その日を
If you'd call our eternally distant future together that, then I'd like to go there with you, to take a peek at that day.
愛しき人よ 抱きしめていて
My beloved, hold me like you always do,
いつものように優しい時の中で この手握って見つめて今だけを
and through all these sweet, tender moments, take my hands, and only have eyes for what's happening right here and now.
You're everything
あなたと離れている場所でも
I may be apart from you where I am now,
会えばきっと許してしまう どんな夜でも
but if I ever saw you, I'd forgive you on any given night.
You're everything
あなたの夢見るほど強く 愛せる力を勇気に 今変えていこう
I'm going to take the strength that makes me able to love you so much I dream of you, and turn it into courage.
You're my everything
You're everything
あなたと離れている場所でも
I may be apart from you where I am now,
会えばいつも消え去って行く 胸の痛みも
but when I do get to see you, the ache I feel in my chest always fades away.
You're everything
あなたが想うより強く 優しい嘘ならいらない
I love you more than you think. I don't need your kind lies,
欲しいのはあなた
all I want is you.
You're everything
my everything
Blessings for your birthday
Blessings for your everyday
最後の一秒まで 前を向け
Face forward until the very last second.
剥がしても何故か増えていくタグと
No matter how much you peel them off, the tags just keep increasing.
ランク付けされていく理不尽な価値観
An unfair sense of worth given by rankings.
そんな数値で人を推し量らないでと
Don't judge people by such numbers,
飛び交う言葉を手で覆い隠した
We covered the colliding words with our hands.
Oh… it's time to get up 灯火を消す前に
Oh... it's time to get up, before turning off the lights.
Oh… it's time to get up 足元を照らせ！
Oh... it's time to get up, light up your feet!
ほら ここを じっと 見つめてみて
Look closely right here,
最高の味方が映ってるでしょ？
Your greatest ally is reflected there, right?
それは命の証
That is the proof of life.
Blessings for your birthday
Blessings for your everyday
例え明日 世界が滅んでも
Even if the world were to end tomorrow,
Blessings for your birthday
Blessings for your everyday
最後の一秒まで 前を向け
Look forward until the very last second.
hip hip hooray これから先も
Hip hip hooray, from now on too.
hip hip hooray 君に幸あれ
Hip hip hooray, I hope happiness finds you.
Blessings for your birthday
Blessings for your everyday
例え綺麗事だって構わない
Even if it's just a meaningless platitude,
Blessings for your birthday
Blessings for your everyday
この世に生まれてきてくれてありがとう
Thank you for being born into this world.
hip hip hooray これから先も
Hip hip hooray, from now on too.
hip hip hooray 君に幸あれ
Hip hip hooray, I hope happiness finds you.
Blessings for your birthday
Blessings for your everyday
例え明日 世界が滅んでも
Even if the world were to end tomorrow,
Blessings for your birthday
Blessings for your everyday
最後の一秒まで 前を向け
Look forward until the very last second.
Blessings for your birthday
Blessings for your everyday
ここに集まった奇跡にありがとう
Thank you for the miracle of bringing us together here.
hip hip hooray これから先も
Hip hip hooray, from now on too.
hip hip hooray 君に幸あれ
Hip hip hooray, I hope happiness finds you.
hip hip hooray これから先も
Hip hip hooray, from now on too.
hip hip hooray 君に幸あれ
Hip hip hooray, I hope happiness finds you.
hip hip hooray
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much.
Blessingをお聞きいただきました！
I hope you enjoyed "Blessing"!
あー！
Oh dear...
大変だみんな間違えちゃったよ！
Everyone made so many mistakes!
この曲で「Blessing」っていう発音がね、ちょっとね、
That song, "Blessing", has really tricky pronunciation,
Neneにはねだいぶあの、あの、難しくて
So Nene found it pretty difficult,
ちょっと難易度高かったわ！
And the difficulty level was high!
これからも練習したいと思います！
So I want to keep practicing it from now on.
マッスルマッスル！
Muscle, muscle!
はい、というわけで、ええと待って、
Yes... so um...
間違えたことで緊張度が上がって、
Because I made mistakes, my tension went way up,
何もわかんなくなってきちゃったので、
And I couldn't figure out what was going on,
お水飲んで落ち着きます。
So I'll drink some water to calm down.
あ、よしよし、よしよし、オッケーオッケー。
Ah, okay, okay.
よし、というわけでじゃあね、今はすごいあのエモエモな感じの曲を聞いてもらったので、
Alright, so now, we just listened to a very emotional song,
ちょっとエモくなったかどうか微妙なんだけれど。
I'm not sure if it actually felt emo or not, though!
え、次次はね、あの、ザ・アイドルみたいな曲を、
Now, next up, we're going to do a classic idol-type song,
この桜並木のステージで、あの、ヒーローしたいと思います！
Right here on this cherry blossom stage, to get hyped up!
わーい！すっごい、やったー！やったやったやったやった！
Yay, yay, yay, yay!
え、アイドルっぽい曲って何かなって思った時に、
When wondering what an "idol-like" song would be,
昔ね、Neneが観てたアニメで、あのめちゃめちゃアイドルしてる子がいて、
I remembered an anime Nene used to watch back then,
そのね曲をちょっと今回はお借りして、え、踊っていきたいと思いますので、
So we're going to borrow that song and dance to it today!
よかったらみんなさん聞いてください！
If you'd like, everyone, please listen!
というわけで、次の曲、えー、ハッピークリセント！
And so, the next song is...
黒板 そっちのけ で チラリ 見つめる 先 は
Glancing sideways at you while ignoring the blackboard,
甘い 横顔 ファンタジー
your sweet profile is a fantasy.
突然 校舎 の 裏 相談 恋愛 モード
Suddenly, behind the school building, it's romantic consultation mode.
やっぱ 私 に じゃ ない
Of course, it's not for me,
だけど あなた の ため に 頑張る
but I'll do my best for your sake.
いつの日 に か 振り向かせてみせる わ
Someday I'll make you turn and look at me!
鈍感すぎだよロミオさん
You're way too dense, Mr. Romeo.
ハッピーハッピーハッピー クレセント
Happy, happy, happy crescent,
あなたに ハッピー プレゼント
a happy present for you.
わかってほしいのこの気持ちあなただけよ 永遠ロマンス
I want you to realize this feeling, just for you, an eternal romance.
ハッピーハッピーハッピー クレセント
Happy, happy, happy crescent,
あなたに全部ささげる I love you
I give you everything, I love you.
いつか終わるの？ねぇ 抱きしめてほしい 片想い
When will this unrequited love end? Please hold me close.
窓辺 溜め息 色 ふいに 見つめる 先 に 暗い 横顔 ミステリー
By the window, a sigh, looking at the gloomy profile of you—a mystery.
走る 渡り廊下 背中 失恋 モード
Running down the hallway, unrequited love mode.
もしもしかして振られたの？
Could it be you were rejected?
元気出してよわたしがいるよ
Cheer up, I am here for you!
告白だよ？でも気づいてない顔
It's a confession? But your face is so clueless.
鈍感すぎだよロミオさん
You're way too dense, Mr. Romeo.
トキメキ ハッピー クレセント
Thumping, happy crescent,
ドキドキ もっと プレゼント
thumping more, present.
気づいてほしいの 胸の鼓動 奏でてるよ 恋のメロディ
I want you to notice, playing the melody of love with my heartbeat.
トキメキ ハッピー クレセント
Thumping, happy crescent,
あなたに 全部 ささげる I want you
I give you everything, I want you.
いつになるだろう ねぇ 終わらせたいよ 片想い
When will it be? Please end this unrequited love.
元気出してよわたしがいるよ
Cheer up, I am here for you!
告白だよ でも気づいてない顔
I'm confessing, but you still haven't realized.
鈍感すぎだよロミオさん
You're way too dense, Mr. Romeo.
ハッピーハッピーハッピー クレセント
Happy, happy, happy crescent,
あなたに ハッピー プレゼント
a happy present for you.
わかってほしいのこの気持ちあなただけよ 永遠ロマンス
I want you to understand this feeling, just for you, an eternal romance.
ハッピーハッピーハッピー クレセント
Happy, happy, happy crescent,
あなたに全部ささげる I love you
I give you everything, I love you.
いつか終わるの？ねぇ 抱きしめてほしい 片想い
When will this unrequited love end? Please hold me close.
ドキドキ もっと プレゼント 気づいてほしいの胸の鼓動奏でてるよ恋のメロディ
Thumping, happy crescent, playing a love melody.
トキメキ ハッピー クレセント
Thumping, happy crescent,
あなたに 全部 ささげる I want you
I give you everything, I want you.
いつになるだろう ねぇ 終わらせたいよ
When will it be? I want to end this unrequited love.
元気出してよ わたしがいるよ
Cheer up, I am here for you!
告白だよ でも気づいてない顔
I'm confessing, but you still haven't realized.
鈍感すぎだよロミオさん
You're way too dense, Mr. Romeo.
あ、どうもありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
え、ハッピークレセントを楽しんでくれましたか？
Did you enjoy "Happy Crescent"?
ハッピーハッピーハッピー クレセント
Happy, happy, happy crescent,
あなたに ハッピー プレゼント
a happy present for you.
わかってほしいのこの気持ちあなただけよ 永遠ロマンス
I want you to understand this feeling, just for you, an eternal romance.
ハッピーハッピーハッピー クレセント
Happy, happy, happy crescent,
あなたに全部ささげる I love you
I give you everything, I love you.
いつか終わるの？ねぇ 抱きしめてほしい 片想い
When will this unrequited love end? Please hold me close.
ドキドキ もっと プレゼント 気づいてほしいの胸の鼓動奏でてるよ恋のメロディ
Thumping, happy crescent, playing a love melody.
トキメキ ハッピー クレセント
Thumping, happy crescent,
あなたに 全部 ささげる I want you
I give you everything, I want you.
いつになるだろう ねぇ 終わらせたいよ
When will it be? I want to end this unrequited love.
せーの 片想い ありがとう！
Thank you so much!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
えーハッピークレセントという曲をお聞き、お聞きいただきました？
Did you enjoy listening to "Happy Crescent"?
聞いていただけました！
I hope you enjoyed it!
ちょっと待ってね、お水。
Hold on a second, some water.
いやいや、ちょっとみんなにはね、あの、ほら
Well, everyone, you see,
元気なね、姿しか見えてないと思うけど、ね、足見せよ！美脚美脚！
since you can only see my head, let's show off our outfits!
でも、まだまだ頑張りますので、頑張ります。
Even so, I'm still working hard, so I'll keep trying!
えーっと、えー、じゃあ、えー夕方、昼の部来て、夕方の部来たら
Next up, let's see... afternoon stage, then evening stage.
次はなんとなんと、夜の部ですねってわけでステージ移動したいと思うんですけど
After that, what could be next? Night stage, right? Time for a stage change, I think.
なんとね、夜の部、一か所、
And guess what? The night stage...
前回から変わったところがあるらしいので、みなさんそれも探しなが、え、お楽しみくださーいってことで
There are changes from last time, so everyone, please search for them and enjoy!
夜の部へ、移動ー！
Now, let's head to the night stage! Move!
銀河の隅で 惑星はグルグル回る
In a corner of the Milky Way, the planets go round and round
電波の記録 エコーが返ってきた
A recording of radio waves, an echo returned
これで何回だ
How many times is this?
遠くの宇宙で あなたに恋をしたんだ
In the distant cosmos, I fell in love with you
届かないこと 分かってるのに
Even though I know it's unreachable
ああ あなたに逢いたいな って気持ちがループ ループする
Ah, I want to see you—my feelings loop and loop,
頭がどうにかなりそうだ それ以外交わせない
my head is about to go crazy, I can't exchange anything else
ああ 今すぐ逢いたいな って来る日もループ ループする
Ah, I want to see you right now—the coming days loop and loop,
この周回軌道上に あなたがいなくても
Even if you're not on this orbit,
そこに大体 愛があるだけ
There, generally, is only love
声を辿って 何光年だ
Following your voice, how many light-years is it?
延長線に消えてゆく
Disappearing into the extension line
このままパッと 忘れられたら
If I could just forget it all in a flash,
楽だろうなあ
It would be so easy
触れられないのに 見えてしまって どうしようもないや
Even though I can't touch you, I end up seeing you, and I can't do anything about it
遠くで近い あなただ 分かってるよ
You're close yet far, I understand that
ああ それでも逢いたいな って何度もループ ループする
Ah, still I want to see you—I loop and loop so many times
心があなたで鳴っている それだけでいいよ
My heart is ringing with you, that alone is enough
ああ 星が周るように ぼくらはずっとループする
Ah, just like how the stars turn, we keep on looping forever
想いが軌道を描いている あなただけを追うよ
My feelings are drawing an orbit, only chasing after you
ああ 今すぐ逢いたいな って命がループ ループする
Ah, I want to see you right now—my life loops and loops
この周回軌道上に あなたがいなくても
Even if you're not on this orbit,
それ以外想えない そこに大体 愛があるだけ
I can't think of anything else. There, generally, is only love
そこに大体 愛があるだけ
There, generally, is only love
そこに大体 愛があるだけいえもう
There, generally, is only love, yeah
そこに大体 愛があるだけおーいぇー
There, generally, is only love, oh yeah
そこに大体 愛があるだけ
There, generally, is only love
よし よし よし ちょっと
Okay, okay, okay, wait
みんな ちょっと 待って待って
Everyone, wait, wait, wait
みんな見ないで 今 はあ
Everyone, don't look right now, hah
はい オカメナサカオッケーです オッケーでーす
Yes, okay, okay!
はい ねねです！
Hi, it's Nene!
はい、というわけで
So anyway,
惑星ループ お聞きいただきました！いえーい！
you just heard Planet Loop! Yay!
この曲ね、あのすっごくずっとね飛んでるからさ
This song, you know, since I'm jumping the whole time,
あの心臓がめっちゃもう、あの…
my heart is beating like crazy, um...
心臓が心臓ってなるんだこの曲
My heart feels like it's going to burst in this song!
でもすごい楽しい曲でしょ、惑星ループ
But it's a super fun song, right? Planet Loop.
なんかね、この動きとっても簡単だし みんなもね、あの
The choreography is really simple too, so everyone...
マネしてほしいかな。今後ねねがまた歌う機会があったらみんなくるくるくるくる回ってね。
I hope you'll copy it. If I get to sing it again, spin around and around, okay?
はい、えーというわけでですね、あの
So, um, with that said,
次がね、あの今回、今回のライブで最大級にあの踊りが忙しい曲となりますので
the next song is one of the most dance-intensive tracks of this live,
ちょっとねねは息を整えてから、え、次に行きたいと思います。
so Nene needs to catch her breath before moving on to the next one.
あ、そうだ、みんな、あのステージのさ、変わったところさ、分かったみんな？
Oh right, everyone, did you notice what changed on the stage?
あ、ねねに夢中でみんなあの分かってなかったでしょ、正直。
Ah, you were all too mesmerized by Nene to notice, weren't you?
ねねばっかあの見てたでしょ？スクリーンしてたでしょ？
You were just staring at Nene, taking screenshots, right?
ステージ分かった人どこだったと思う？
For those who noticed, where do you think it changed?
え、深呼吸が今までと違う。ねねが疲れてるだけだよみんな。
Ah, my deep breaths sound different? Nene is just tired, everyone!
分からなかった？でしょでしょ。じゃあちょっとあの
You didn't know? Thought so. Well then,
ねねのこの上のほうに注目してください。
please pay attention to the upper part of Nene.
どーん！
Ta-da!
え、見て、これ見てわかる？みんな何が違うか。
Look at this, can you tell what's different?
なんとなんとこれ、スーパーネネチステージってね、書いてある看板みたいなところが、あのピカピカになりました！いえーい！
Believe it or not, the sign that says "Super Nenechi Stage" is now all shiny and sparkly! Yay!
ありがとう！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you so much!
なんか前回お披露目の時は間に合わなくて、あの今日の、今日に間に合うようにね
Since we didn't make it in time for the last debut, we worked hard to get it ready for today
あのめちゃくちゃ頑張って作りました。
and made it happen.
ありがとうございます！大感謝！
Thank you! Huge thanks!
やった！ほら見て、引きで見た時にね、全然あのスーパーネネチ感が違うでしょ？
Yay! See, when you look at it from afar, the Super Nenechi vibe is totally different, right?
はい、というわけで、え、ねねの息整えましたので、え、次の曲に行きたいと思いますみんな。
Alright, with that, Nene has caught her breath, so I'd like to move on to the next song, everyone.
次はね、あのみんな大好き、ハニワさんの曲から1曲歌いたいと思います。
Next up, I want to sing a song from HoneyWorks, whom everyone loves.
それでは聞いてください、「ヒロイン育成計画」。
So please listen to "Heroine Training Plan".
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で 王子様にチヤホヤされるでしょ
Surely a heroine would be pretty and pampered by a prince, right?
芋女の私もお姫様になれたかなんてね イェイ
Could a plain country girl like me ever become a princess? Yay!
バイト探し
Searching for a part-time job,
採用ないし
no one hires me,
やけになって飛び込む
desperate, I dive right in
場違いすぎる世界
to a world way out of my league.
パシリばかり
Just an errand runner,
雑用係
a chore girl,
最悪の奴らのマネージャー就任です
appointed manager to the worst guys around.
バレたら最後
If I get caught,
奴隷なのは嫌だし
becoming a slave is out of the question—
生きるためだし
it's just to survive!
やけになって飛び込む 場違いすぎる世界
Desperate, I dive right in to a world way out of my league.
走りばかり 雑用係
Errand runner, chore girl...
あ、ちょっと待って！あ、ちょっとスタッフさんストップ！
Ah, wait a second! Ah, staff, stop!
あー、もう一回やりたい！
Ah, I want to do it again!
止まった？
Did it stop?
何語句なった？
What happened to the music?
おれ？助けて～！
Me? Help me~!
何かが
Something is...
あ、ごめんねみんなちょっと。ほら、ねねがポーズ取っているからそれ見ててよ。
Ah, sorry everyone. Look, Nene is striking a pose, so watch that!
トラブルは突っつきもんだよなみんな！いえーい！いえーい！
Troubles are meant to be poked at, right everyone! Yay! Yay!
ねねのダンスが激しすぎて、あのマイクがついてこれなくなった、これだな。困ったぜ。
Nene's dancing was so intense that the microphone couldn't keep up. What a pain.
やっぱスーパーネネチ一味違うわみんな。アップで見ちゃってねのこと。ほら、二箇所あったの、脇。
As expected, Super Nenechi is in a different league, everyone. Look at me up close. See, there are two spots—armpits!
じゃあちょっと、これを機にちょっと休憩にしようかな。
Well then, maybe I'll take a little break now.
あ、やだ、ちょっとネタバレしちゃったじゃあみんなにダンス。
Ah, no, I just spoiled the dance for everyone.
あ、聞こえる聞こえる。
Ah, I can hear it, I can hear it.
えっと、え、スタッフさん、BGMが非常に小さくねねの声が大きいという状況になっております。
Um, staff, the BGM is extremely quiet while Nene's voice is super loud right now.
よし、オッケーオッケーだみんな。お待たせしました！お待たせ！
Alright, okay okay everyone. Sorry for the wait! Thanks for waiting!
みんな、あ、ちょっと待ってな、ねねの、ねねの耳に入ってくる声が爆大、爆大、爆大、爆笑だいだいだ。
Everyone, ah, wait a second, the sound coming into Nene's ears is super loud, huge, huge, haha.
あ、あ、あ、もう一個大きくがいい。
Ah, ah, ah, one more bigger is good.
あ、よしよし、あ…
Ah, there, there, ah...
ああー！あー、ありがとうございます！
Ahh! Ah, thank you so much!
あ、いい感じ。
Ah, feels good.
あ、どうする？どうやって立て直す？みんな。
Ah, what should I do? How do we bounce back, everyone?
えー、いぇーい！
Uh, yay!
え、それでは次は、え、みんなが、え、大好きな、あのハニワさんから1曲歌わせていただきたいと思います！
Now, next up, I'd like to sing a song by everyone's favorite HoneyWorks!
え、それでは、え、さっきの記憶はみんなのぶっ飛ばしていただいて、
So everyone, please completely blast away the memory of just now,
え、それでは、え、広い育成計画聴いてください！
and please listen to "Heroine Training Plan"!
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で
Surely if I could be the girl of your dreams,
王子様にチヤホヤされるでしょ？
lights on me, all shining, like a true princess?
芋女の私もお姫様になれたらなんてね（イエーイ）
What kind of dream is that for a plain girl like me? (Yay!)
バイト探し 採用なしで
Job hunting, zero success,
やけになって飛び込む 場違いすぎる世界
I recklessly jumped into a world where I don't belong at all.
パシリばかり 雑用係
Always running errands, doing odd jobs,
最悪な奴らのマネージャー就任です
appointed as the manager for the worst guys ever.
バレたら最後 嬲られるのは嫌だし
If I'm found out, I'll be teased, and I hate that,
生きるためだし
but I'm doing this just to survive!
パシリばかり
Always running errands,
雑用係
doing odd jobs,
最悪な奴らのマネージャー就任です
appointed as the manager for the worst guys ever.
バレたら最後 嬲られるの
If I'm found out, I'll be teased—
なんてね イエーイ
just kidding, yay!
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で
Surely if I could be the girl of your dreams,
王子様にチヤホヤされるでしょ？
lights on me, all shining, like a true princess?
芋女の私もお姫様になれたらなんてね
What kind of dream is that for a plain girl like me?
私をプロデュースして
Style me up and produce me,
髪も服も全部可愛くして
make my hair and clothes super cute!
いつか出会う王子様どこで何をしているの？神様
Where are you, my destined prince? What are you doing, God?
待ってますから気長に
I'll be waiting patiently for you!
ある日出会う 運命の人
Then one day, meeting my destined person,
紳士な振る舞いにドキドキしちゃったんだ
his gentlemanly behavior made my heart race.
名前なんて聞けるはずない
There's no way I could ask his name,
また会いたいなんて願っているだけでした
I could only wish that we would meet again.
時間が止まる「また会えたね」と君
Time stops as you say, "We meet again,"
やっぱり恋だ
this has got to be love.
きっと少女漫画じゃ両思い
Surely in shoujo manga we'd be mutually in love,
ベタでいいじゃん もしやベタがいいじゃん
clichés are great, maybe clichés are best!
モブ女の私もヒロインなる気ありますなんてね
Even a background girl like me wants to be the heroine!
すぐにくっついちゃえばいい
We should just get close right away,
悲劇いらない いいね？シェイクスピア
no tragedies needed, right, Shakespeare?
やっと会えた王子様 まずは名前を知ることだよ
The prince I finally met, first I need to know his name!
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で
Surely if I could be the girl of your dreams,
王子様にチヤホヤされるでしょ？
lights on me, all shining, like a true princess?
芋女の私もお姫様になれたらなんてね
What kind of dream is that for a plain girl like me?
すぐにくっついちゃえばいい
We should just get close right away,
悲劇いらない いいね？シェイクスピア
no tragedies needed, right, Shakespeare?
やっと会えた王子様 まずは名前を知ることだよ
The prince I finally met, first I need to know his name!
ヒロインらしく自然に
Naturally, like a true heroine,
それじゃったって最悪な奴らに
but those worst guys said to me,
これじゃダメだ100振られるってどうすればいいのー！？
"That won't do, you'll be rejected 100 times, what should you do?!"
気持ちなら負けないなんてみんな同じこと思ってて
Everyone thinks the same—that they won't lose in feelings—
そこからの勇気と押しが大事なんです聞いてる！？
and from there, courage and persistence are what matter, are you listening?!
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で
Surely if I could be the girl of your dreams,
王子様にチヤホヤされるでしょ？
lights on me, all shining, like a true princess?
芋女の私もお姫様になれるのなんてね
What kind of dream is that for a plain girl like me?
自信ちょっとついたよ
I've gained a little confidence now!
当たって砕けたらバカにして笑ってよお願い
If I fail, make fun of me and laugh, please!
行ってきますね告白
I'm going to confess now—
ヒロインになれ今日から
become a heroine starting today!
あー、おっけー！ふうー、ふうー、ふうー。お疲れ様！
Ah, okay! Whew, whew, whew. Great job!
SUPER NENECHI STAGE
ちょっと、あの、みんな、ねね、あの、花のウォーターのほうが…
Um, everyone, Nene, um, the flower water...
見えちゃうと、あぶなかったー！
If it's visible, that was close!
はい、というわけで、広い育成計画をお聞きいただきましたー！
So, having listened to this broad training plan,
ま、みんなには聞こえないと思うけどね、あ、思い切り2回も歌っちゃった！ありがとう！
well, you probably couldn't hear it, but I accidentally sang it twice! Thank you!
はい、えーというわけで、あのですね、今回はここのステージで終わりじゃなくて、
Yes, so, the thing is, this time it doesn't end at this stage,
ねねがね、今まで1回も歌ったことのないステージって、今回は最後に、えー2曲、
at a stage Nene has never sung at before, we'd like to finally sing two songs,
歌させていただきたいと思います。
I'd like to perform them for you.
えーというわけで、移動したいと思います！ホロアリーナへ、レッツゴー！
So with that, let's move over! To Holo Arena, let's go!
まだこの世界は 僕を飼いならしたいみたいだ
Still, this world seems like it wants to tame me
望み通りいいだろう 美しくもがくよ
As you wish, I'll beautifully struggle
互いの砂時計 眺めながらキスをしようよ
Let's kiss while watching our hourglasses
「さよなら」から一番 遠い 場所で待ち合わせよう
Let's meet at a place farthest from "goodbye"
辞書にある言葉で 出来上がった世界を憎んだ
I hated a world made of words found in a dictionary
万華鏡の中で 八月のある朝
Inside a kaleidoscope, on a certain August morning
君は僕の前で 恥ずかしそうに笑ってみせた
You smiled shyly in front of me
この世界の教科書のような笑顔で
With a smile like a textbook of this world
ついにときは来た
Finally, the time has come
昨日までは序章の序章で 飛ばし読みでいいから
Up to yesterday was just a prologue, you can skim through it
ここからが僕だよ
From here on is my story
経験と知識と カビの生えかかった勇気を持って
Armed with experience, knowledge, and moldering courage
今だかつてないスピードで 君のもとへダイブを
I'll dive to your side at an unprecedented speed
まどろみの中で 生ぬるいコーラに
In the slumber, in a lukewarm cola
ここで無いどこかを 夢見たよ
I dreamed of somewhere else not here
教室の窓の外に 電車に揺られ運ばれる朝に
Outside the classroom window, on a morning carried by a swaying train
愛し方さえも 君の匂いがした
Even the way of loving smelled like you
歩き方さえも その笑い声がした
Even the way of walking sounded like your laughter
いつか消えてなくなる 君のすべてを
All of you, which will one day disappear
この目に焼き付けておくことは
Burning it into my eyes
もう権利なんかじゃない 義務だと思うんだ
Is no longer a right, I believe it's my duty
運命だとか未来とかって 言葉がどれだけ手を伸ばそうとも届かない
No matter how far words like "fate" or "future" stretch out their hands
場所で僕ら恋をする
We fall in love in a place they cannot reach
時針の針も二人を 横目に見ながら進む
Even the clock hands move forward while looking at us sideways
まだこの世界は 僕を飼い馴らしていたみたいだ
It seems the world still wants to tame me.
望み通りいいだろう 美しくもがくよ
If that's the way, I will obey, beautifully struggling.
互いの砂時計 眺めながらキスをしようよ
Let's kiss while watching each other's hourglasses.
「さよなら」から一番 遠い 場所で待ち合わせしよう
Let's meet at a place furthest from "goodbye."
ついに時はきた 昨日は序章の序章で
The time has finally come, yesterday was a prologue to the prologue.
飛び越し読みでいいから ここからが僕だよ
Just skimming through is fine, right here is where I start.
経験と知識と カビの生えかかった勇気を持って
With experience, knowledge, and moldy courage,
いまだなかつてないスピードで 君のもへとダイブを
I'll dive to you at an unprecedented speed.
まどろみの中で 生生しいコーラに
In a slumber, into a lukewarm cola,
ここでないどこを 夢見たよ
I dreamed of somewhere other than here.
教室の窓の外に 電車に揺られ 運ばれる朝に
Outside the classroom window, on a morning carried by a swaying train,
愛し方さえも 君の匂いがした
Even the way of loving had your scent.
歩き方さえも その笑い声がした
Even the way of walking had your laughter.
いつか消えてなくなる 君のすべてを この目に焼き付けておくことは
Keeping everything of you, which will someday disappear, burned into my eyes,
もう権利なんかじゃない 義務だと思うんだ
is no longer just a right, I believe it's a duty.
運命だとか未来とかって 言葉がどれだけ手を伸ばそうとも届かない 場所で僕ら恋をする
Words like fate or future, no matter how far they stretch, cannot reach where we fall in love.
時針の針も二人を 横目に見ながら進む
Even the hands of the clock look at us sideways as they move forward.
そんな世界を二人で 一生 いや、何章でも 生き抜いていこう
In a world like this, let's live through it for a lifetime, no, through countless chapters!
「はじめまして」なんてさ 遥か彼方へと追いやって
Pushed "nice to meet you" far away into the distance,
1000年周期を 一日で息しよう
let's breathe a thousand-year cycle in a single day.
辞書にある言葉で 出来上がった世界を憎んだ
I hated the world completed by words in the dictionary.
万華鏡の中で 八月のある朝 君は僕の前で
Inside the kaleidoscope, on a morning in August, you stood in front of me,
はにかんでましなして見せた この世界の教科書のような笑顔で
acting shy and composed, with a textbook smile of this world.
嘘みたいな日々を 規格外の意味を
Days like a lie, meanings out of the ordinary,
悲劇でいいから望んだ
I wished for them even if they were tragedies.
そしたらドアの外に 君が全部抱えて立っていたよ
Then outside the door, you were standing there holding everything.
運命だとか未来とかって 言葉がどれだけ手を伸ばそうとも届かない
Words like fate or future, no matter how far they stretch, cannot reach...
場所で僕ら遊ぼうか
the place where we play.
昨日だと思ったんだ
I thought it was yesterday.
運命だとか未来とかって 言葉がどれだけ手を伸ばそうとも届かない 場所で僕ら恋をする
Words like fate or future, no matter how far they stretch, cannot reach the place where we fall in love.
そんな世界を二人で 一生 いや、何章でも 生き抜いていこう
In a world like this, let's live through it for a lifetime, no, through countless chapters!
横目に見ながら進む
Let's sweep away the time...
まだこの世界は 僕を飼い馴らしていたみたいだ
It seems the world still wants to tame me.
望み通りいいだろう 美しくもがくよ
If that's the way, I will obey, beautifully struggling.
互いの砂時計 眺めながらキスをしようよ
Let's kiss while watching each other's hourglasses.
「さよなら」から一番 遠い 場所で待ち合わせしよう
Let's meet at a place furthest from "goodbye."
あーというわけで、スパークを聴いていただきました！ありがとー！
Ah, and that was "Sparkle"! Thank you so much!
みなさんどうでしたか？ねねのおかげでちょっとでも元気が出たらいいな！ありがとね！
Thank you all so much for watching me today!
わかりました。みんな、ラストと次が1曲目になるんですけど、
Got it. Everyone, the last and next songs are the first song, but...
え、何の曲だと思う？みんな。
Uh, what song do you think it is, everyone?
まだ1曲目だけさ、ほら、ね、といえばさ、ほら。
We're only at the first song, you see, you know, speaking of "Ne", look.
え、ちょっとねがさ、1杯目のあの曲が、あの曲があるでしょ、みんな。
Uh, Nene's first song, that song, you know that song, right everyone?
あの、あの曲だよ。みんなもう知ってる、知ってる、あの曲だよ。
That, that song. Everyone already knows it, that song.
あれをね、最後にみんなね、え、元気よく歌って、元気にこのライブを締めたいと思いますので、
At the very end, everyone, let's sing it cheerfully and wrap up this live concert with good energy,
皆さんよかったら最後の1曲なので、最後まで聞いていってください！今日は見てくれてありがとうございました。
so everyone, if you'd like, since it's the last song, please listen all the way to the end! Thank you very much for watching today.
え、それでは最後の曲、え、聞いてください。
Uh, well then, please listen to the final song.
え、ねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねね大爆走！
Nenenenenenenenenenenenenenene! Super Dash!
ななななな「な」じゃなくて
Nana nana, it's not "na,"
ににににに「に」じゃなくて
Nini nini, it's not "ni,"
ぬぬぬぬぬ「ぬ」じゃなくて
Nunu nunu, it's not "nu,"
ののののの「の」じゃなくて
No nonono, it's not "no,"
……「ね」！
...and it's "ne"!
（ねね！）
(Nene!)
こんねね～！
Konnene~!
（こんねね～！）
(Konnene~!)
ホロライブ5期生 オレンジ担当
Hololive 5th Generation's orange rep,
桃鈴ねね です！
Momosuzu Nene!
（ねねち～！）
(Nenechi!)
異世界から来ました
Coming from another world,
アイドル志望の
an aspiring idol,
新人Vtuber（何だって！？）
a newbie VTuber (What!?)
まぁ、とにかくいきましょう！
Well, anyway let's keep going!
ちょっとくらい緊張したって、スベったって「おうー！」って感じでさ
Even if I'm a bit nervous or mess up, shouting "Oh!" and going
「どりゃあ！」ってやっていこう
with "Doryaa!"
あきらめの悪さは長所だよね？
Being bad at giving up is a strong point, right?
ねねねねねねねねね（ね！）ねねねねねねねねね（ね！）
Ne nenene nenene nenene! (Ne!) Ne nenene nenene nenene! (Ne!)
「はいぁ～ん」なこともあるけど
Sometimes things get tough,
悔しいこともあるけど
and sometimes they're frustrating,
大丈夫！今日もしっかり
but it's alright! Today too,
おめかしして
getting all dressed up nicely,
いつかはきっと「スーぱーねねちー！」
someday I'll surely be "Super Nenechi!"
ついてきてね ねねねねねね
Come along with me, ne nenene nenene
ねねねねねね ねねねねねね（ねね！）
ne nenene nenene ne nene nene (Nene!)
ねねねねねね ねねねねねね（ね！）
nene nene nene ne nene nene (Ne!)
って、全力でいこう！
And go at full power!
そんで全開でいこう！
Yep, let's go at full throttle!
思い切りやれば何とかなるよ
If I give it my all, it'll somehow work out
ポンコツだっていい（よいしょ！）
Being clumsy is fine (Yoisho!)
誤字ったっていい（よいしょ！）
Making typos is fine (Yoisho!)
ただ駆け抜けていこうよね（ね！）ね！（ね！）ね！
I'll just keep running through (Ne!) Ne! (Ne!) Ne!
大爆走！（ねね！）
Super Dash! (Nene!)
野菜ジュースと炭酸とお菓子
Veggie juice, soda, and sweets,
そろえて準備OK！
I've got them all ready, OK!
でも朝は苦手（だね！）
But I'm bad at mornings (That's right!)
夜も苦手（だね！）
And bad at nights too (That's right!)
やっぱり睡眠って、大事だよね？
Sleeping really is important, huh?
ねねねねねね ねねねねねね（ね！）
Ne nenene nenene nenene! (Ne!)
たくさんの人に愛されタイ！
I want to be loved by lots of people!
ちゅちゅちゅ！ちゅちゅちゅ！
Chu chu chu! Chu chu chu!
大好きなみんなに愛されタイ！
Loved by my beloved fans!
ちゅちゅちゅ！ちゅちゅちゅ！
Chu chu chu! Chu chu chu!
そしたらなるんだ「はいぱーねねちー！」
And then I'll become "Hyper Nenechi!"
って、全力でいこう！
And go at full power!
そんで全開でいこう！
Yep, let's go at full throttle!
歌は誰にも負けたくないんだ
I don't want to lose to anyone in singing!
大きい声で（よいしょ！）
With a loud voice (Yoisho!)
あ、その前に（よ、いしょ！）ちょっとトイレ行ってくるね～
Ah, before that (Yoisho!) I'll go to the restroom real quick~
(restroom time！！！)
(Restroom time!!!)
ただいま～！
I'm back~!
最後に
And finally,
ねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねね
ne nenene nenene nenene...
って、全力でいこう！そんで全開でいこう！
Let's go at full power! Go at full throttle!
思い切りやれば何とかなるよ
If I give it my all, it'll somehow work out
ポンコツだっていい（よいしょ！）
Being clumsy is fine (Yoisho!)
誤字ったっていい（よいしょ！）
Making typos is fine (Yoisho!)
ただ駆け抜けていこうよね（ね！）ね！
I'll just keep running through (Ne!) Ne!
大爆走！
Super Dash!
それじゃあまたねね～
Well then, see you later~
（またねね～）
(See you later~)
ばいば～い！
Bye-bye!
ねねねねねねねね！大爆走
Nenenenenenenene! Big Rampage
ねねいろらいぶ 3D Streaming
Neneiro Live 3D Streaming